He didn't mean that.
(Bernadette:)So I should probably explain
why I kind of fibbed.
(Howard:)That would be nice.
(Bernadette:)I told my dad that
you were the one
(Bernadette:)who didn't want kids because I
didn't want to disappoint him.
(Howard:)But you were okay
throwing me under the bus?
(Bernadette:)Turns out yeah,
I didn't think twice about it.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Bernie, you don't need
to worry about me.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)But I don't want
to see you miss out.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Raising children
(Mr Rostenkowski:)was the most rewarding
experience of my life.
Oh, please.
Mom did everything.
(Bernadette:)All you did was
come home from work,
(Bernadette:)sit on the couch and drink beer.
(Bernadette:)How is that raising kids?
(Mr Rostenkowski:)This is really
(Adam:)a conversation
for husband and wife.
(awkward chuckle) I'm gonna go clean up,
hit the road.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)If your mother asks,
I was here till 10:00.